Guide to the Cornell University Women's Judiciary Board records, 1923-1962.
Cornell University Women's Judiciary Board records, 1923-1962.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Women's Judiciary Board records, 1923-1962.
34-10-1130
Cornell University. Women's Judiciary Board.
1 cubic ft.
Reports, minutes, historical material, case files, and records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes reports, minutes of board and committee meetings, historical material, case files, and other records of the Cornell University Women's Judiciary Board.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes reports, minutes of board and committee meetings, historical material, case files, and other records of the Cornell University Women's Judiciary Board.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Women's Judiciary Board.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
College discipline.; Women college students.
Form and Genre Terms:
Case files.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
Individual case files: restricted to permission of student for 80 years after the creation of the record.
CONTAINER LIST
- Records, minutes
  - 1923-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1937-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Sororities and dormitory cases
  - 1947-1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Comstock "B" (Sage) 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Individual cases
  - 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Judiciary matters and history
  - 1917-1962 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - no date (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Reports
  - 1953-1960 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Applications
  - 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Joint meeting, Men's Judiciary Board
  - 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)